她在那裏有寶寶
而紐納茲正在計劃把城市燒掉
一個土耳其女子被發現在第三樓死亡
我們正在接觸約會嘅地方，約翰會在等你
我不確定會發生什麼事
你知道怎麼使用那枚槍吧？
嗯？
蛤？
凱爾文街，佛洛克，現在
我們嘅計劃改變了
為何突然變了心？
為何要殺亂約翰？
我稍後會處理他，現在就這麼説吧
總統洛夫會很失望地聽到這個消息
他個人要求你殺亂約翰
他相信你是工作人員
我不在乎
我不會接受任何人嘅要求
我會自行殺亂約翰
現在趕快到凱爾文街去吧
凱爾文街
要求你殺亂約翰
現在是時候教他一項課程了
這地方無論如何都會燒焦
讓他們留在這裏等着燒焦
救命啊
別哭了，小子，唔好哭了
你媽媽很快就會回來
艾謝
我…
我不敢相信你還活着
你找到我了嘛？
這是因為迪達嘅事
他告訴我你住在這裏，你説了迪達？
那就説了你那天跟我説嘅天馬男人了
迪達在哪？
他沒來過嘛？
呃…沒有
那他去哪了？
你看見了艾謝嘛？
這孩子是艾謝嘅小孩
他很想她，他很想他嘅媽媽
也不可能…不，這不可能
我不相信
這小子真可憐
他太年輕了，卻沒有母親
我要做什麼？
她是最後嘅
必須沒有其他犯人
現在我必須見到現在嘅特區領導人
大家有什麼想法？
把城市燒焦了？
不可能
我們經常聽到謊言關於右派極端人
我們冇法反對他們每次威脅我們
更令我驚訝嘅是這位日本人在這裏跳舞
雖然他説自己嘅性命在危險中
你們倆怎麼回事？
艾謝死了
你們不明白嘛？
她死了是因為她嘗試提醒
我們所有人這個危險
我也有疑問
她像你一樣是個女人吧？
你們女人經常和德國人分手
但卻失去了一切，這不是新事物
你們把我們土耳其人都弄壞了
無論如何
我們都不知道那個人是誰嘅孩子
你們都知道生命是很困難嘅事
你們應該知道比噉樣做更好
如果你們想要生命
你們必須要聽我嘅話
忘了
做你想要嘅事
你們可以燒掉，去死吧
無論如何都好
現在等一等
你們在推薦軍隊嘛？
也許我們應該按照這位日本人所説嘅做
我們沒有什麼失去嘅
Mr， Deniz
你們真嘅會聽一啲我們不認識嘅亞洲人嘛？
他可能有點懷疑
但是世界上有很多有信心嘅日本人
例如，總統諾基
總統諾基？
他是誰？
你説你不認識他嘛？
總統諾基是一名勇敢嘅日本人
他們在歐洲失敗時拯救了土耳其軍隊
哦
馬上去收拾我們所有嘅軍人
看起來真好吃
咱們進去吧
不必急着，女士們
請慢用時間
我們不想要吃完，才可以享受娛樂
我已經計劃好
當主題嘅演出結束後，演出將會達到尾聲
同時，我們來享受這76座嘅旅遊
我特地為了這晚嘅節奏
Mmm， the
first dish we will
indul ge in is
my favorite， raw
fl ounder
with caviar
Mmm…
And as the
feast begins…
哦
Voila
the first fire
What a
wonderful start
But like I
told you， that's
still just
an appetizer
Where is the
main course？
Remember
what I said
Don't be impatient
如果你喜歡吃飯
我嘅節目會是你真正嘅喜悦
告訴我主要嘅項目在哪兒？
如果那是一個飲料，那你會燒什麼？
我們需要更多火炎炸彈
我們要分開，其餘嘅男人跟我來
正如我所想，火炎開始了
這整個地方都會爆炸
三個團隊，救女生和孩子
我嘅真是個美麗嘅驚喜
為何我們要這個尊貴呢？
為何你…別嘗試了
還是跟你老闆説再見吧
把那個危險嘅東西放下吧
為何我們不一起享受這頓飯呢？
可惜嘅是，你嘅飲料嘅味道不太好
別擔心，那只是一開始而已
這就係你最愛嘅吧？
對唔住
別這麼反對，寶貝
你看，畢竟這是一場
美麗嘅慶祝，為了約翰
聽我講，約翰不想有任何這種事
哦？
告訴我，你怎麼這麼肯定呢？
我看到了，用自己嘅眼睛
我跟隨他嘅訊息，我知道他想要什麼
約翰不在乎你嘅計劃
所以，你到底看到了什麼？
約翰…
他不想有任何這種事，你明白嘛？
沒問題，放鬆一下…放輕鬆一點
約翰死了是因為你
今晚，我不會讓任何人都死
所以，你到底想要做什麼？
你想要在什麼地方開火？
糟糕
開火了
把受害人帶到醫院，我在那裏
天馬
你找到了彼得嘛？
有人告訴我，他們看到了一個像
他那樣嘅小孩，在午夜嘅旁邊
彼得，我嘅
嘿
我們唔好跟着她，再把她帶回來嘛？
不，我們繼續吃午餐吧
那個女人確實是…我猜她應該是在家裏嘅
她嘅眼睛…
她真嘅想要把我殺了
幸好她還沒發現
我很快就給她了主要嘅位置
那，我們要去拿下一道菜了嘛？
不，先給我一點衣服
她真是個可怕嘅女孩
你做到了
你會好好，雙方都行，好嘛？
她聽不到你是誰，王女，但謝謝我放逃嘅
你倆acaba到那裏？
咦，我…
女士，你想知道出了什麼事？
這個傢伙把我連殺了
忘了這是什麼，我要趕到這兒了
如果那是那個少嘅打火機穿衣雞
我不會太驚訝
這是第二句話
這是第三句話
I won't have
any more victims
not one more
我不會有更多嘅犧牲，再也沒有一個
Wait，whatareyoutalkingabout？
Well，thewind'
sgonnachangedirection
It always
happens every
night around
this time， the
wind just stops
Then it starts
blowing towards
town from
where the river is
然後它就開始向城市飛來
The wind…
it stopped
風…它停了
And now…現在…
…it's time
for the main
course to
be served
時間讓主隊服務
Did you see
them running away？
你看到他們跑掉了嘛？
Allow me to
buy this round
Okay，thatshouldtakecareofit
好嘅，這應該要照顧好
Thanksforpatchingmeup，doctor
謝謝你幫我，醫生
Letmebuyyouadrink
What are you
talking about？
你在説什麼呢？
Youhavetotakeiteasyforawhile
你要輕鬆一點，Oh
comeon，loosenup
doctor， right？
That's right
it's thanks to
you we were able
to put out those
firesandsavetheneighborhood
沒錯，謝謝你
我們可以把那啲火炎放出嚟，救了隔壁
YouunderestimatetheTurks
你不可underestimatetheTurks
Where are they t
ending to all of
the other
injured people？
The mosque
by the river
在河裏嘅墓堂
Hey，Dr，Tenma
takeabreakandrelax
來吧，天馬醫生，休息一下
Come on
why don 't you have a
drink with us？
來吧，為何不給我們喝一杯？
Notuntileveryone'stakencareof
不至於所有人都被照顧了
If all of the
fires up until
now were just
diversions，如果所有
火炎到現在都只是偷渡
where do you
think they're
going to light
the real fire？
你覺得他們會把真正嘅火炎燒到哪裏來？
How the hell
would I know？
我怎麼知道呢？
I don 't give a
shit about this
stupid town anyway
我也不關心這個愚蠢嘅城市
Besides
there's something much
more important
on my mind that
I gotta
take care of
除此之外，我必須要照顧更
重要嘅事情，Wait
I need you to
tell me， and I
need you to
tell me now
我必須要你告訴我現在
Where would you
start the real
fire？
Get your
hands off of me
Like I already
told you， the
wind'sgonnacomefromtheriver
像我已經告訴過你，風會從河
裏來，Listento？
Yes，thisisgoingtobedelicious
聽聽看…是嘅，這會很美味
We 're right
on schedule
The celebration of the master
race is
about to begin
聖戰嘅慶祝快要開始了
It's you
Why did you
follow me？
你嚟？
BecauseIhavetoputoutthefire
I made a
promise to Tenma
我答應了天馬
Tenma…天馬…
This is it
這就係它
It's the warehouse
這就係廠房
Thank goodness
Looks like
they haven't found
this place yet
謝謝睇嚟他們還沒找到這裏
These are
all filled with
chemicals？
If all of this
were to go up
it'd be hopeless
There'dbenothingleftofthetown
I'll protect
this place no
matter what
I'm not
gonna let those
horrible
people burn it down
Are you okay？
I slipped
我掉了
What the
heck is this？
這是什麼東西？
It smells
like gasoline
聞起來像汽油
It looks like…
someone's there
看起來…有人在那裏
It'salright
I'm fine
I can walk
on my own
Let's get you
to a shelter so I
canhaveacloserlookatit
I twisted my ankle
It probably
happened when I
wastryingtogetawayfromthefire
我彎了我嘅腳，我可能是想要離開火嘅事
Now that I
finally got this
rug， who gives a
damn about this
stink in' town？
I bet I can
probably get
800，000 marks
for this baby
No， a million
我想我可能可以給這孩子800
000分，不，10000
Heckle
What happened to Dieter？
Couldn 't say
He'sprobably…
呃，不能説，他可能…
Where is he？
Where'd he go？
What happened to him？
他在哪裏？
Last I saw
he was going to the
abandonedwarehousebytheriver
最後我看見，他在海邊嘅遺産中間走過了
Whythere？
The wind's gonna
blow in from the
river soon
海邊嘅風將會馬上吹進
Soifthechemicalsin
that warehouse
are set on fire
it's all over
for this town
所以如果那間沙發中的化石都放在火上
這城市就全都完了
ThisiswhatIwastalkingabout
這就係我所説嘅
Tell everyone
to evacuate from
theriversidesheltersrightaway
Go
You 're going
to take me there
你們要帶我去
Who is it？
Who's back there？
Who
is it？
Can it be true？
Are you really
Johan's sister？
是真嘅嘛？
Put the
lighter down now
把燈燈放下
Once I set
this trail of
gasoline on
fire， this
warehouse is
going to go up
in an instant
I'm going to
shoot you in the
head before
that happens
我會先把你射到頭來
I can fire
quicker than you
can flick that
lighter， and I'm
not afraid to do it
我可以比你射得更快，而且我不會害怕
And what
if you miss？
你會失敗嘛？
I haven't
skipped a day of
training in six
months straight
soIknowIcanhityoufromhere
You don't
fright en me
Don't you know？
This is a
celebration of
the master race
你不怕我嘛？
ThisisourbigwelcomeforJohan
But Johan doesn
't want any of
the things you want
但Johan不想要你想要嘅東西
Yes， it's
true that he was
recentlyseenhereinFrankfurt
是嘅，他在這裏最近被看到了
And all of
his subordinates
He left a
message behind
you know
他還留下了一個信息，你知道嘛？
What message？
Listen to me
Johanisnotthepersonyouthinkheis
The truth
is much more
complex than that
What are you
trying to say？
你在説什麼？
It's worse
Itmustbeterrifyingforhim
He's suffering
He's in anguish
and teetering on
the edge
of despair
更糟糕嘅是，他在痛苦中，在悲哀中
You know
I'm not so sure it's
such a good
idea to be making
enemies of
these guys
你知道，我不太確定這是這麼好嘅主意
I didn't sign on
for all of this
I'm going to
call it a day
See ya
我還沒結帳，再見
Where the hell
do you think you
're going？
Where the hell
do you think you
Are you just
going to let
Diet er die
like that？
Tellmewherethewarehouseis
你到底想要讓彼得死嘛？
Alright
I'll tell you
Just let me go
You're choking me
好啦，我會告訴你…讓我走，你在騙我
Youtoldmeaboutyourfriend
YousaidthathisnameisTenma，right？
你告訴我你朋友嘅事
你説他嘅名字叫Tenma，對嘛？
Would you
believe that I
knowamanwhosenameisTenmaalso？
你相信我也知道他嘅名字
叫Ten ma嘛？
Yes
But he must
never fire a
gun，notifIcandoitforhim
沒錯，但他必須不會用槍
如果我能做到嘅話，就不行了
I don't want
him to kill anyone
He's a good man
我不想他殺人，他是個好人
K illing people
is always wrong
you understand？
Even if they'
re the bad guys？
Right
Don'teverdowhatI'mabouttodo
沒錯，別再做我現在要做嘅事
Close your eyes
Don't look
別看
Don't shoot
別開槍
Tenma
天馬
Quick，Hekko
putoutthefire
快啲，Hekko，開火
And use the
rock， hurry
No
Not the rock
不用石頭
One million
marks
Gone
一百萬，沒了
Nina
妮娜
Tenma
天馬
Damn it， all the
cops are coming
Get out， go
I'll take care
of things here
我來處理事情，There'
saboatoverbytheriver
河裏有一艘船，Please
Tenma，youhavetoleavenow
拜託，天馬，你現在就要離開了
My main course
it got cold
我嘅主船，它變冷了
Thank you
for all your
cooperation
young lady
謝謝你所有嘅協力，女士
We'd appreciate
it if you'd come
down to
the station
我們會很感激你下船
Wait one second
okay？
I'll be right back
等一下，我馬上回來
Hey，holdon
You have
to promise me
something， Nina
Sweartomeyouwon'tkillanyone
I saw it
I saw Yohan
's message
I saw it， too
I'm heading there now
我也看到了
Ten years ago
the night I shot
my brother
十年前，那天我叫了我兄弟
I finally know
what he meant
when he told me
to shoot him in
the head
我終於知道他想要把他打死嘅意思了
Now I understand
現在我明白了
Yohan
he's not alone
There are two
of him inside
Yohan，他不是獨自嘅
That's why， Dr
Tenma， it wasn't
your fault
你是為了什麼
You didn't do
anything wrong
你沒做錯
I must do it
我必須做
I have no
other choice
我沒有其他選擇
I have to
shoot Yohan again
我必須再次殺Yohan
Hey
wait up
Whatthehellarewedoinghereanyway？
Come on
let's get out of here
來吧，我們出去吧
Thanks
I give up
There's no use
with this guy
不用再給他打死了
I guess he'll
be starving and
broke forever
我猜他會餓死了
If only I
still had that rug
Damn it
Whatthehellisthatsupposedtobe？
It's a message
它是一個訊息
Help
The monster
inside me is
about to explode
我嘅裏面嘅怪物快要爆炸了
Whatisthissupposedtomean？
He has a
split personality？
這是什麼意思呢？
他有個分屬性嘛？